horizen.global 2019-04-05

# Privacy Policy

Zen Blockchain Foundation, a Delaware nonprofit corporation (“Horizen,” “we” or “us”) is committed to protecting the privacy and security of your personally identifying information. We have prepared this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, protect, and disclose your Personal Information and Usage Data (as those terms are defined below) when you use any of the Horizen websites or services (the “Services”). This Privacy Policy also explains how you can manage your information preferences. By using the Services you consent to this Privacy Policy. 

## 1\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT

### PERSONAL INFORMATION

When you register for the Services, or utilize the Services, we may collect information that personally identifies you, such as your name, address, mobile telephone number, e-mail addresses and other information that you provide to us (“Personal Information”). You may be asked to provide us with certain Personal Information when you register to use the Services, and at other times. The decision to provide this information is voluntary. However, if you choose not to provide the requested information, you may not be able to use certain features of the Services.

### USAGE DATA

We automatically collect usage information that allows us to collect information regarding how users access and use the Services (“Usage Data”). For example, when you download and use the Services, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use and the device identifier (or “UDID”). Additionally, each time you use the Services, we automatically collect information regarding the type of web browser you use, your operating system, your Internet Service Provider, your IP address, the pages you view on our sites, the time and duration of your visits, crash logs and other information relating to your use of the Services. We use this information to analyze trends, administer the Services, troubleshoot any user problems, and to enhance and update the Services.

### COOKIES

Like many other websites, we use cookies on our sites (a small removable data file that is stored by the web browser on your computer that identifies your computer and browser when you visit our site or use our Services). We do not use cookies to collect Personal Information but rather to improve the quality of the Services. Most web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. THE SITE’S COOKIES DO NOT AND CANNOT INFILTRATE A USER’S HARD DRIVE TO COLLECT ANY INFORMATION STORED ON THE HARD DRIVE.

## 2\. HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We use information we collect for internal purposes only. We do not sell or rent information about you. We will not disclose Personal Information to third parties without your consent. We use Usage Data only to monitor and improve the Services. For example, we use Google Analytics to help analyze how users use the Service. Google Analytics uses cookies to collect information such as how often users visit the site, what pages they visit, and what other sites they used prior to coming to the Service. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve our Service. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit the Service, rather than your name or other personally identifying information. We do not combine the information generated through the use of Google Analytics with your Personal Information. Although Google Analytics plants a persistent Cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique member the next time you visit the Service, the Cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to the Service is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy.

## 3\. HOW WE PROTECT THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

### SECURITY

Horizen is committed to protecting the security of your information. We employ industry best security measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. Regardless of our efforts, no data transmission over the Internet or other network, including any of the Services, can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Accordingly, we cannot and do not guarantee the absolute security of any information you transmit on or through the Services and any information you transmit is sent at your own risk.

### COMPLIANCE WITH LAWS AND LAW ENFORCEMENT

Horizen cooperates with government and law enforcement officials to enforce and comply with the law. We may therefore disclose Personal Information and Usage Data and any other information about you, if we deem that it is reasonably necessary to: (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process (such as a subpoena or court order) or enforceable governmental request; (b) enforce the Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations thereof; (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Horizen, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

### YOUR INFORMATION MAY BE MAINTAINED WITHIN THE UNITED STATES

Please be aware that we may process and store information in the United States. By using the Services, you agree that the collection, use, transfer, and disclosure of your information and communications will be governed by the applicable laws in the United States. The majority of data we collect is stored on servers located in the United States and Europe. Accordingly, we may transfer and store data outside of your home country. When we transfer data out of the European Economic Area or Switzerland, we make use of the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks, EU-approved standard contractual data protection clauses, binding corporate rules for transfers to data processors, or other appropriate legal mechanisms to safeguard the transfer.

## 4\. MISCELLANEOUS

### POLICY TOWARDS MINORS

Our Services may not be used by anyone under 18. We do not knowingly collect information on anyone under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18 you must stop using our Services immediately.

### ACCURACY

You can always review, correct, update, or change your Personal Information. Upon your request, we will: (1) correct, update or change your Personal Information; (2) stop sending you messages if you wish to opt out of our direct marketing efforts; and/or (3) disable your account to prevent any future activity through that account. You may make any of these requests by emailing the request to support@horizen.global. Please do not email any sensitive information.

### RETENTION

We retain information only for so long as it continues to help us monitor or improve the Services. The exact length depends on the type of information collected and processed. When Personal Information or Usage Data is no longer needed it will be automatically deleted or anonymized.

### COMPLIANCE WITH GDPR

To the extent required by law, Horizen complies with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). GDPR gives users the following rights:

  * Right of erasure (right to be forgotten)
  * Right of rectification
  * Right to be informed
  * Right of access
  * Right to restrict processing
  * Right to data portability
  * Right to object
  * Right not to be subject to automated decision making
  * Right to complain to a supervisory authority

If you do not believe that Horizen is in compliance with GDPR, please email your concerns to support@horizen.global.

### LINKS TO OTHER SITES

Please be aware that the Services may contain links to other sites that are not governed by this Privacy Policy. Horizen is not responsible for the content or practices of these sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of each site visited before disclosing any personal information.

### CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY

We may periodically change this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will inform you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Site. Those changes become effective upon posting on our site, the date of which is shown as the “Revised On” date in the revised Privacy Policy. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. By continuing to use the Services, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

### CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please e-mail them to info@horizen.global. Horizen is a Delaware nonprofit corporation. Please send physical mail to:

Zen Blockchain Foundation  
701 Gervais Street, Suite 150  
Columbia, South Carolina 29201  
USA
